[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1972 musical won 8 Academy Awards but not the Best Picture Award.", "correct_answer": "Cabaret", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago", "My Fair Lady", "Gigi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Cats have 517 of these in their entire body.", "correct_answer": "Muscles", "incorrect_answers": ["Claws", "Whiskers", "Bones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Shawshank Redemption, what was Reds jail cell number?", "correct_answer": "237", "incorrect_answers": ["125", "416", "444"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term piggy bank derives from the word pygg, an orange type of clay that used to be made into jars in which people kept their money.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The legal drinking age in a few US states is 18.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin B12 is a set of complex chemical compounds synthesized in nature only by this group of organisms.", "correct_answer": "Bacteria", "incorrect_answers": ["Fungi", "Plants", "Animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Was the male Moa larger than the female?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first privately financed craft to go into outer space?", "correct_answer": "SpaceShipOne", "incorrect_answers": ["The SpaceX Dragon", "MIR", "SpaceHab"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rain forests are home to approximately what percentage of all the living animal and plant species on the planet?", "correct_answer": "65%", "incorrect_answers": ["12%", "24%", "80%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Bernard Fockers occupation before he became a father according to the 2004 comedy movie Meet the Fockers?", "correct_answer": "He was an attorney.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was a doctor.", "None of these", "He was a painter."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2008 movie is a shot-for-shot remake of the 1997 Austrian film of the same name.", "correct_answer": "Funny Games", "incorrect_answers": ["Ambrose, Louisiana", "The Omen", "The Echo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following places in Greece is NOT an island?", "correct_answer": "Kavala", "incorrect_answers": ["Alonissos", "Ithaka", "Kythira"]}]